[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Brazilian wandering spiders are included in Guinness World Records 2007 as the worlds most venomous spiders. How do they inject their venom?", "correct_answer": "By biting", "incorrect_answers": ["By stinging", "All of these", "By urticating hairs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of fish is traditionally used for the making of the Spanish stew called Marmitako?", "correct_answer": "Tuna", "incorrect_answers": ["Pike", "Carp", "Mackerel"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "As massage relaxes the body, relieves pain and reduces stress, it contributes to this.", "correct_answer": "Better sleep", "incorrect_answers": ["Hair growth", "Stronger bones", "Open mindedness"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What movie featured the humanoid robot, named Gort?", "correct_answer": "The Day the Earth Stood Still", "incorrect_answers": ["Star Wars Franchise", "Short Circuit", "Batteries Not Included"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was originally selected to play Leo Bloom in the 1968 comedy film The Producers written by Mel Brooks?", "correct_answer": "Dustin Hoffman", "incorrect_answers": ["Zero Mostel", "Jimmy Broderick", "Luther Adler"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the motion picture From Russia With Love, what S.P.E.C.T.R.E. agent is an expert in chess?", "correct_answer": "Kronsteen", "incorrect_answers": ["Gobinda", "Whitaker", "Fekkesh"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Do Gary and his brothers provide services by sea in their business?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Males of this whale species have one tooth that can grow to be 10 feet (3 m) long.", "correct_answer": "Narwhal", "incorrect_answers": ["Strapped-tooth whale", "Long-finned pilot whale", "Blainville\u2019s beaked whale"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these Asian tortoise species is a very popular pet in many countries around the world?", "correct_answer": "Russian Tortoise", "incorrect_answers": ["Cuora", "Keeled Box Turtle", "Rafetus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which statement, regarding James VI of Scotland and James I of England, is true?", "correct_answer": "They are one and the same person.", "incorrect_answers": ["They are father and son.", "They are brothers.", "They lived two centuries apart and are not related."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The science known as theriology or therology studies which of the following?", "correct_answer": "Mammals", "incorrect_answers": ["Land animal species", "Carnivorous animals", "Endemic animal species"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This vitamin of the B complex, popular also under the name vitamin H, is not included in the recommended daily intake by some health organizations.", "correct_answer": "Vitamin B7", "incorrect_answers": ["Vitamin B9", "Vitamin B12", "Vitamin B15"]}]